<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Documentation on Imageless Thought</title>
    <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/documentation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Documentation on Imageless Thought</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/documentation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Generative AI and Microsoft Copilot</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/documentation/ms-linkedin-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/documentation/ms-linkedin-ai/</guid>
      <description>The content in this article was created from my notes from the certification course, Career Essentials in Generative AI by Microsoft and LinkedIn with summarization and revisions performed using Microsoft Copilot.
Introduction What is Generative AI? Generative AI is changing how we create. (light music) For the first time, humans are supervising and machines are generating. It&amp;rsquo;s helping us lift the dirty, dull, dangerous and difficult tasks from humanity&amp;rsquo;s shoulders so then we can simply focus on the very essence of our work, the vision, the idea, and the purpose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Universal Digital Signage: Installation Instructons</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/documentation/digital-signage-install/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/documentation/digital-signage-install/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Universal Digital Signage&lt;/strong&gt; web application provides a centralized digital signage solution. Images can be uploaded to the server and playlists created online.  Playlists can be assigned to individual digital signs (&lt;strong&gt;hosts&lt;/strong&gt;) or signs can be managed in groups. Playlist changes can be performed on a schedule (daily, weekly, or monthly schedules) with an option to add an &lt;em&gt;interrupt&lt;/em&gt; schedule change (a temporary change set for a given period of time after which the sign or group reverts back to its normal schedule).  There is also the option to assign playlists to &lt;strong&gt;channels&lt;/strong&gt; to provide slideshows for other use cases (such as screensavers, external groups, or anythng where a slideshow is needed), &lt;strong&gt;interactive kiosks&lt;/strong&gt;, and hosted online &lt;strong&gt;presentations&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
