<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Imageless Thought</title>
    <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mbaggett/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Imageless Thought</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://imagelessthought.github.io/mbaggett/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Github Professional Essentials</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mbaggett/projects/github-linkedin-cert-transcript/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mbaggett/projects/github-linkedin-cert-transcript/</guid>
      <description>Practical Github Actions Introduction Creating a MarketPlace GitHub action When you&amp;rsquo;re applying for a job, employers want to see samples of work that gives them a good idea of your abilities. In this course, I&amp;rsquo;m going to show you how to build the type of project that employers would love to see, a GitHub Action that&amp;rsquo;s featured in the GitHub Marketplace. We&amp;rsquo;ll be working in a variety of languages and formats like Python, shell scripts, YAML, XML and Docker containers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Career Essentials in Generative AI by Microsoft and LinkedIn: Transcript</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mbaggett/projects/ms-linkedin-ai-transcript/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mbaggett/projects/ms-linkedin-ai-transcript/</guid>
      <description>What is Generative AI? Introduction Generative AI is changing how we create. (light music) For the first time, humans are supervising and machines are generating. It&amp;rsquo;s helping us lift the dirty, dull, dangerous and difficult tasks from humanity&amp;rsquo;s shoulders so then we can simply focus on the very essence of our work, the vision, the idea, and the purpose. It&amp;rsquo;s a complete paradigm shift for the future of jobs. I am Pinar Seyhan Demirdag and I&amp;rsquo;m the co-founder and the AI director of Seyhan Lee.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
