<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Imageless Thought</title>
    <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Imageless Thought</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence: Demystifying AI, Machine Learning, and Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/blog/artificial-intelligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/blog/artificial-intelligence/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Artificial Intelligence (AI) is a multidisciplinary field focused on creating machines capable of performing tasks that traditionally require human intelligence. Its diverse applications range from natural language processing to image recognition, offering profound implications for various industries. Within the vast landscape of AI, Machine Learning (ML) stands out as a subset that emphasizes the development of algorithms enabling machines to learn from data and improve their performance.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Github Professional Essentials</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/projects/github-linkedin-cert-transcript/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/projects/github-linkedin-cert-transcript/</guid>
      <description>Practical Github Actions Introduction Creating a MarketPlace GitHub action When you&amp;rsquo;re applying for a job, employers want to see samples of work that gives them a good idea of your abilities. In this course, I&amp;rsquo;m going to show you how to build the type of project that employers would love to see, a GitHub Action that&amp;rsquo;s featured in the GitHub Marketplace. We&amp;rsquo;ll be working in a variety of languages and formats like Python, shell scripts, YAML, XML and Docker containers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Career Essentials in Generative AI by Microsoft and LinkedIn: Transcript</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/projects/ms-linkedin-ai-transcript/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/projects/ms-linkedin-ai-transcript/</guid>
      <description>What is Generative AI? Introduction Generative AI is changing how we create. (light music) For the first time, humans are supervising and machines are generating. It&amp;rsquo;s helping us lift the dirty, dull, dangerous and difficult tasks from humanity&amp;rsquo;s shoulders so then we can simply focus on the very essence of our work, the vision, the idea, and the purpose. It&amp;rsquo;s a complete paradigm shift for the future of jobs. I am Pinar Seyhan Demirdag and I&amp;rsquo;m the co-founder and the AI director of Seyhan Lee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Started with Github and Github Pages</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/blog/github-announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/blog/github-announcement/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://git-scm.com&#34; title=&#34;Git Website&#34;&gt;Git&lt;/a&gt; is a free and open source distributed version control system designed to handle everything from small to very large projects with speed and efficiency. Git is widely used for collaborative software development and &lt;strong&gt;Github&lt;/strong&gt; is a very popular Git platform. Git is used to track changes, keep a complete history of the changes, and allows you to roll back to any point. Owners can grant access to a project and allow others to submit changes: those changes can be reviewed by the owner and merged, rejected, or a separate branch created.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jekyll: Static Webpages</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/blog/jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/blog/jekyll/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://jekyllrb.com/&#34; title=&#34;Jekyll Website&#34;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt; is a free and open source static site generator that was developed by Github and is written in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ruby-lang.org/en&#34; title=&#34;Ruby Programming Language&#34;&gt;Ruby Programming Lanaguage&lt;/a&gt;. It takes text written in &lt;a href=&#34;https://daringfireball.net/projects/markdown/&#34; title=&#34;Markdown Website&#34;&gt;Markdown&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Shopify/liquid/wiki&#34; title=&#34;Liquid Website&amp;quot;&amp;gt;Liquid&#34;&gt;Liquid&lt;/a&gt;, HTML &amp;amp; CSS and uses standardized layouts to create static webpages. &lt;a href=&#34;https://sass-lang.com/&#34; title=&#34;SASS Website&#34;&gt;SASS: Syntactically Awesome Style Sheets&lt;/a&gt; integration is bulit-in. You can easily customize the look and feel, URLs, and the data displayed on your pages.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Generative AI and Microsoft Copilot</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/blog/ms-linkedin-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/blog/ms-linkedin-ai/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Generative AI and Microsoft Copilot This document is an article that explains the concept, history, and applications of generative AI, a type of AI that can create new content. It also introduces Microsoft Copilot, a tool that uses generative AI to assist users with various tasks in Microsoft 365 applications.&#xA;What is Generative AI? Generative AI is a paradigm shift for the future of work, where humans supervise and machines generate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Python for Non-Computer Science Students</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/blog/python/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/blog/python/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the world of Python programming! This tutorial is designed for undergraduate students who may not have a background in computer science but want to learn the basics of Python. Python is a versatile and powerful programming language that has gained widespread popularity for its simplicity, readability, and flexibility. Python is beginner-friendly and widely used in various fields, including data science, web development, and automation. It was created by Guido van Rossum and first released in 1991, with the goal of making programming accessible and enjoyable. Named after the British comedy group Monty Python, the language has evolved into a dynamic and user-friendly tool used across various domains of information technology.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to YAML for Non-Computer Science Students</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/blog/yaml/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/blog/yaml/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;YAML, short for &amp;ldquo;YAML Ain&amp;rsquo;t Markup Language&amp;rdquo; or sometimes &amp;ldquo;Yet Another Markup Language,&amp;rdquo; is a human-readable data serialization format. It is often used for configuration files and data exchange between languages with different data structures. YAML files use indentation and colons to denote structure, making them easy to read and write.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub: Version Control</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/tech-links/github/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/tech-links/github/</guid>
      <description>GitHub is a platform and cloud-based service for software development and version control, allowing developers to store and manage their code. It uses Git software, providing the distributed version control of Git plus access control, bug tracking, software feature requests, task management, continuous integration, and wikis for every project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Digital Signage: Installation Instructions</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/documentation/digital-signage-install/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/documentation/digital-signage-install/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Universal Digital Signage&lt;/strong&gt; web application provides a centralized digital signage solution. Images can be uploaded to the server and playlists created online.  Playlists can be assigned to individual digital signs (&lt;strong&gt;hosts&lt;/strong&gt;) or signs can be managed in groups. Playlist changes can be performed on a schedule (daily, weekly, or monthly schedules) with an option to add an &lt;em&gt;interrupt&lt;/em&gt; schedule change (a temporary change set for a given period of time after which the sign or group reverts back to its normal schedule).  There is also the option to assign playlists to &lt;strong&gt;channels&lt;/strong&gt; to provide slideshows for other use cases (such as screensavers, external groups, or anythng where a slideshow is needed), &lt;strong&gt;interactive kiosks&lt;/strong&gt;, and hosted online &lt;strong&gt;presentations&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raspberry Pi</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/tech-links/rpi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/tech-links/rpi/</guid>
      <description>Raspberry Pi have all the features required for computing: WIFI, Bluetooth, HDMI, USB, along with ample processing power and RAM.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/tech-links/ubuntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/tech-links/ubuntu/</guid>
      <description>Ubuntu is my preferred Linux distribution for a desktop OS. It is well maintained and the documentation and tutorials are plentiful. Pro subscriptions are available for free for personal use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red Hat</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/tech-links/redhat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/tech-links/redhat/</guid>
      <description>Red Hat Enterprise Linux is my preferred choice as a server OS. They are the maintainers of Ansible, an open-source solution that I have used for endpoint configuration of Linux devices and servers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postman: API Platform</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/portals/postman/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/portals/postman/</guid>
      <description>Postman is an API platform for building and using APIs. Postman simplifies each step of the API lifecycle and streamlines collaboration so you can create better APIs—faster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACI Learning</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/training/aci/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/training/aci/</guid>
      <description>ACI Learning is another training resource I use. ACI Learning courses are broken down into half-hour, self-contained chunks. Much more engaging than other training options and the have apps for most devices, including Apple tvOS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub: Version Control</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/portals/github/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/portals/github/</guid>
      <description>GitHub is a platform and cloud-based service for software development and version control, allowing developers to store and manage their code. It uses Git software, providing the distributed version control of Git plus access control, bug tracking, software feature requests, task management, continuous integration, and wikis for every project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discord</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/portals/discord/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/portals/discord/</guid>
      <description>Discord is a social-media collaboration platform with servers organized into channels by topic. Collaborate and communicate with instant messaging, VOIP, and video chats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft 365: Online Access to Applications and Collaboration Tools</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/portals/o365/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/portals/o365/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft 365 is a product family of productivity software, collaboration and cloud-based services developed by by Microsoft. It encompasses online services and applications formerly part of the Microsoft Office Suite: Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook, among others.&#xA;Use the link above to login to your Microsoft 365 account, this will launch the online version of Microsoft Outlook: The other available applications can be accessed by using the icon at the top left.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stormwind Studios</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/training/stormwind/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/training/stormwind/</guid>
      <description>Stormwind Studios is a training resource I use to maintain my skill set and knowledge base. They provide live and on-demand bootcamp courses from wide-range of vendors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coursera</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/training/coursera/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/training/coursera/</guid>
      <description>Coursera is a leading online learning platform for higher education, where more than 49 million learners from around the world come to learn skills of the future. UNT is among the world’s top universities and industry educators to partner with Coursera to offer courses, Specializations, certificates, and degree programs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LinkedIn Learning</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/training/linkedin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/training/linkedin/</guid>
      <description>LinkedIn Learning offers the widest range of offerings of any service, from technical to business. LinkedIn Learning is a great place to find training for your supported users when introducing or migrating to a new service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft: Azure Cloud Computing</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/portals/azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/portals/azure/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Azure is a cloud computing platform which offers access, management, and development of applications and services through global data centers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Digital Signage</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/blog/digital-signage/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/blog/digital-signage/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The signage solution we have in place has served us well but it is time for an update. The original open source developer of the solution has taken their project proprietary as well. We will be developing the new solution as open source and will use already available code whenever possible: don&amp;rsquo;t reinvent the wheel.  Unless you have to, that is.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>W3 Schools</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/training/w3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/training/w3/</guid>
      <description>W3Schools is a freemium educational website for learning coding online. Initially released in 1998, it derives its name from the World Wide Web but is not affiliated with the W3 Consortium. W3Schools offers courses covering many aspects of web development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft: Learning Paths</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/training/microsoft/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/training/microsoft/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft offers their self-paced technical training, including learning labs, for free online to everyone. Certification tests and instructor-led training are available but are not free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple: IT Training</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/training/apple/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/training/apple/</guid>
      <description>Apple offers their technical training for free online to everyone. Certification tests are available but are not free. There are considerably fewer training offerings, when compared to Microsoft.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JAMF: Apple Endpoint Management</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/training/jamf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/training/jamf/</guid>
      <description>JAMF provides a complete enterprise management and security solution for Apple devices. Both on-premise and cloud solutions are available. Easy to manage and enterprise-secure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux Kernel Organization</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/training/linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/training/linux/</guid>
      <description>The Linux Kernel Organization is managed by The Linux Foundation, which provides full technical, financial and staffing support for running and maintaining the kernel.org infrastructure.t.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux Professional Institute</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/training/linux2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/training/linux2/</guid>
      <description>The Linux Professional Institute is the largest vendor-neutral Linux and open source certification body. Some classes are free to everyone and others require a fee. Certification tests are available for a fee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Academic Technologies</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/campus-links/academic-technologies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/campus-links/academic-technologies/</guid>
      <description>Academic Technologies provides IT governance and shared IT services for the colleges, libraries, and academic departments within the Division of Academic Affairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Subscriptions Discounted for Students</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/campus-links/adobe-buy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/campus-links/adobe-buy/</guid>
      <description>UNT offers discounted personal education subscriptions to the Adobe Creative Cloud: they are available for a one time purchase price of $50 (+$3 processing fee) and are valid until the end of the academic year. Students without a subscription may access some of the Adobe Creative Cloud applications while using a computer in one of the on-premise classrooms or labs at no cost: cloud features and many applications are not available.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emergency Procedures</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/campus-links/emergency-procedures/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/campus-links/emergency-procedures/</guid>
      <description>In the event of an emergency situation (medical, fire or police), the appropriate action is to immediately call 911. For NON-EMERGENCIES, you may contact the UNT Police Department on their 24-Hour Non-Emergency Line: (940) 565-3000. To report a facilities-related issue, you may contact UNT Work Control: (940) 565-2700. More information on emergency responses and campus safety resources can be found at the Emergency Management and Safety Services website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guacamole: Universal Remote-Access</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/campus-links/guacamole/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/campus-links/guacamole/</guid>
      <description>Remote connections to Mac computers on the UNT campus are provided by Guacamole. Guacamole is an HTML 5 web application that allows users to make remote connections to MacOS computers using any modern web browser that supports HTML5. The computer endpoints are located on the UNT campus and are managed by UNT staff. You can connect and use a Mac from any device, regardless of the operating system. The interface is quite simple and intended to be as seamless and unobtrusive as possible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoom: Video-Conferencing</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/campus-links/zoom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/campus-links/zoom/</guid>
      <description>All active UNT employees and students have access to a Zoom One Business subscription, but you must activate your account before you will be able to use it. Activation is a quick and straight-forward process. This website provides you with the information on activating and using your Zoom. If you are hosting a webinar we can provide a staff member or student employee to assist during the webinar (College of Visual Arts and Design).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Subsystem For Linux</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/blog/windows-subsystem-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/blog/windows-subsystem-linux/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Over the past two years years Microsoft has made some significant improvements to the &lt;b&gt;Windows Subsystem for Linux&lt;/b&gt;. The Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL) is a feature of the Windows operating system that enables you to run a Linux file system, along with Linux command-line tools and GUI apps, directly on Windows, alongside your traditional Windows desktop and apps. &lt;b&gt;WSL 2&lt;/b&gt; is a new version of the Windows Subsystem for Linux architecture, available beginning with Windows 10-Version 1903-Build 18362, that powers the Windows Subsystem for Linux to run ELF64 (Executable and Linkable Format) Linux binaries on Windows. WSL2 provides a truly great resource for developers and application testing.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audio-Visual Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/campus-links/audio-visual/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/campus-links/audio-visual/</guid>
      <description>This is a tutorial for using the audio-visual systems in the specialized classrooms (type 210) and other spaces managed by the College of Visual Arts and Design.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASTU 3703.501: Creative Coding | Studio Art: New Media</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/student-web/astu3703/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/student-web/astu3703/</guid>
      <description>An introduction to the fundamentals of coding and computer science as a creative medium.&#xA;Instructor: Ranran Fan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybersecurity</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/skills/cybersecurity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/skills/cybersecurity/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cybersecurity&lt;/strong&gt; is the art of protecting networks, devices, and data from unauthorized access or criminal use and the practice of ensuring confidentiality, integrity, and availability of information. It seems that everything relies on computers and the internet now—communication (e.g., email, smartphones, tablets), entertainment (e.g., interactive video games, social media, apps ), transportation (e.g., navigation systems), shopping (e.g., online shopping, credit cards), medicine (e.g., medical equipment, medical records), and the list goes on.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/repositories/github/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/repositories/github/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guacamole: Remote Access Service</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/status/status-guacamole/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/status/status-guacamole/</guid>
      <description>guacamole.unt.edu&#xA;main.guacamole.unt.edu&#xA;cloud.guacamole.unt.edu</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentations</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/projects/presents/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/projects/presents/</guid>
      <description>This is a collection of personal presentations, some of which may or may not be aligned with or related to the content on this website:&#xA;Example Presentation 1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Digital Signage</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/projects/digital-signage/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/projects/digital-signage/</guid>
      <description>This project is in progress, the content below was created before the project began and changes have occured during the development. Think of this as the pseudo-code of the project.&#xA;Description: This will be a device independent solution: the only configuration of the devices and screensavers that should be required is a URL to the server.. The server will host the content in playlists using one of the available templates. The digital signage device will simply need to launch a browser in full-screen mode and open the URL at startup: the URL will be the server.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Websites</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/status/status-websites/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/status/status-websites/</guid>
      <description>public.cvad.unt.edu&#xA;Online Service Desk&#xA;Booked Scheduler&#xA;Webcheckout&#xA;Papercut/Webprint&#xA;Zoom&#xA;Canvas&#xA;Microsoft Sharepoint</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What training and certificatons have you completed?</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/about/training-certifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/about/training-certifications/</guid>
      <description>Below is the information on the various training and certifications I have completed. I complete training using a variety of vendors, my preferred training vendors are: Coursera (used for my Google and IBM certifications), Stormwind Studios (used for Microsoft and other proprietary software training), ACI Learning (used for open source and new technology training), W3 Schools (provides training certifications that are primarily focused on web technologies and not tied to a specific product), and finally LinkedIN-Learning (provides a wide range of technical and business-related certifications).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT Support Management</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/skills/it-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/skills/it-management/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;IT support refers to the assistance provided to users of technology products or services. This can include end-point management, troubleshooting technical issues, providing training and education, and offering guidance on best practices. An IT support department plays a crucial role in ensuring that technology-related issues are addressed and resolved efficiently. The range of services provided by an IT support department may vary depending on the organization&amp;rsquo;s size, structure, and specific needs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web and UI Design</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/projects/web-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/projects/web-design/</guid>
      <description>Understanding Open-Source Licensing Terms You will find many resources online that you may want to include in your website: images, fonts, themes, templates, plug-ins etc&amp;hellip; Before you use them in your website it is important to check the licensing terms to confirm that your use is in compliance with the agreement. You must follow any stipulations included in the agreement.&#xA;When it comes to open-source resources, many of the licensing terms you will encounter grant you permission to use the resource pretty freely.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridge Training</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/campus-links/bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/campus-links/bridge/</guid>
      <description>UNT Bridge is the primary online training option for university employees. The content is primarily focused on business processes and compliance training. This is where the Annual Cybersecurity Awareness Training is hosted. Some other examples: UNT Ethics and Standards of Conduct, ePRO Coordinator Training, Anti-Bias &amp;amp; Cultural Awareness Training, and the UNT Policies &amp;amp; Title IX: Preventing Discrimination, Harassment, Sexual Misconduct &amp;amp; Retaliation Training.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computing Policies: Acceptable Use and Privacy</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/campus-links/computing-policies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/campus-links/computing-policies/</guid>
      <description>The computing policies specifically for the resources provided by the College of Visual Arts and Design can be found online, here.&#xA;The University of North Texas provides Information Resources for employees, students and authorized individuals to use in conducting official University business and for other purposes as authorized in the Policy: 14.003: Acceptable Use.&#xA;The University of North Texas will inform individuals about information it collects about them, unless the information may be withheld pursuant to state or federal law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coursera</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/campus-links/coursera/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/campus-links/coursera/</guid>
      <description>Coursera is a leading online learning platform for higher education, where more than 49 million learners from around the world come to learn skills of the future. UNT is among the world’s top universities and industry educators to partner with Coursera to offer courses, Specializations, certificates, and degree programs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linked-In-Learning</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/campus-links/linked-in-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/campus-links/linked-in-learning/</guid>
      <description>LinkedIn Learning is provided free of charge to UNT System students, faculty and staff. You can browse through more than 10,000 courses. With the upgrade, in addition to the English library, you have our multi-language access for courses in - German, French, Spanish, Japanese, Mandarin, and Portuguese</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Registrar Training: AD Astra and Courseleaf</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/campus-links/registrar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/campus-links/registrar/</guid>
      <description>The UNT Registrar provides online training or AD Astra, Courseleaf, and other services. This website provides a link to the materaisl for each of the applications provided by their department. The training materials vary by application: some are available as pdfs, while others have full video tutorials.&#xA;Courseleaf is a curriculum management solution that is used by the University of North Texas. CourseLeaf offers five software modules that integrate with each other and your system of record to cover everything from course inception through course registration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safety Training</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/campus-links/safety-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/campus-links/safety-training/</guid>
      <description>&#xA;Prior to using the Digital Fabrication Lab equipment all users must complete a mandatory Safety Training. Use the link above to begibn the safety training. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software: What is available to students?</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/campus-links/software/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/campus-links/software/</guid>
      <description>Follow the link above for a list of the software titles available in the College of Visual Arts and Design spaces. Unless noted, all software is available in each of our learning spaces, the Computer Lab, the Digital Fabrication Lab, and on the UNT Online Computer Lab.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
