<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Online Services on University of North Texas: College of Visual Arts and Design</title>
    <link>/portals/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Online Services on University of North Texas: College of Visual Arts and Design</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/portals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Creative Cloud Webstore</title>
      <link>/portals/adobe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/portals/adobe/</guid>
      <description>This offer is only available to students. Full-time employees and instructors of record receive an educational enterprise subscription as part of their employment. Part-time employees who require the Adobe Creative Cloud for their job duties should contact their department regarding access. Subscriptions are not available for purchase by employees.
Employees may contact their local support team if they are having difficulty accessing their Adobe subscription.
If you are an adjunct or graduate student who is working as an instructor of record during the current semester, contact the local IT department of the college that employed you if you are having trouble accessing the Adobe Creative Cloud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Booked Scheduler: Reservations</title>
      <link>/portals/booked/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/portals/booked/</guid>
      <description>Booked is an online appointment scheduling solution that is available to students, instructors, and staff at the College of Visual Arts and Design at the University of North Texas to make appointments for various services we provide to our users.
If you are an instructor, student or staff member of the College of Visual Arts and Design use the link above to login to your Booked Scheduler account.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canvas: Learning Management System</title>
      <link>/portals/canvas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/portals/canvas/</guid>
      <description>Canvas LMS, is the online learning management solution for the University of North Texas that is available to all students and instructors. Canvas LMS is an open-source Learning Management System that serves as a central hub for online, hybrid, and in-person classrooms. As a modern education tool, Canvas LMS connects teachers and educators to their students.
Use the link above to login to Canvas.
Here are some links to get you started:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft 365: Online Access to Applications and Collaboration Tools</title>
      <link>/portals/o365/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/portals/o365/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft 365 is available to all students, instructors and staff at the University of North Texas. Microsoft 365 is a product family of productivity software, collaboration and cloud-based services developed by by Microsoft. It encompasses online services and applications formerly part of the Microsoft Office Suite: Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook, among others.
Use the link above to login to your Microsoft 365 account, this will launch the online version of Microsoft Outlook: The other available applications can be accessed by using the icon at the top left:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MyLab: Online Computer Lab</title>
      <link>/portals/mylab/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/portals/mylab/</guid>
      <description>MyLab, the online computer lab for the University of North Texas is available for students and instructors to access a Windows (Citrix) or Mac (Guacamole) computer from anywhere, using any device that is capable of running a modern, HTML5 web browser.
Use the link above to access the MyLab Online Computer Labs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Service Desk</title>
      <link>/portals/osd/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/portals/osd/</guid>
      <description>Our college uses Microsoft Teams to provide an online service desk to our students, instructors, and staff. Physical visits to our service desk are rarely required as we can begin a remote session to help with any hardware or software issues - including new software installation. We can begin a remote session with you regardless of whether you are on campus, working at home, or travelling in a foreign country as long as your device is connected to the internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Papercut: Webprint from Any Device</title>
      <link>/portals/webprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/portals/webprint/</guid>
      <description>Papercut, is an online webprinting solution for the University of North Texas that is available for our students, instructors, and staff to submit their print jobs online. Print outs can be picked up at the printer or service location you slect to print to from within the app.
Use the link above to login to your Papercut account.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statistics Software: License Portal</title>
      <link>/portals/stats/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/portals/stats/</guid>
      <description>The Statistics License Portal, is available to all students, instructors and staff at the University of North Texas. You may use this service to acquire licenses for the latest versions of statistics software licensed by the university
Use the link above to login to the Statistics Software License portal for UNT.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WebCheckout: Equipment Checkout</title>
      <link>/portals/webcheckout/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/portals/webcheckout/</guid>
      <description>Webcheckout, is an online equipment reservation solution for the University of North Texas that is available for our students, instructors, and staff to reserve equipment. Equipment can be picked up and returned to the service location shown in the portal.
Use the link above to login to your WebCheckout account.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoom: Video Conferencing</title>
      <link>/portals/zoom/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/portals/zoom/</guid>
      <description>Zoom, is a video-conferencing solution that is available to all students, instructors and staff at the University of North Texas. Online classes use Zoom for their class sessions but it is used widely across campus as a general video-conferencing solution.
Use the link above to login to your Zoom account for UNT.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
