<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Imageless Thought</title>
    <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mbaggett/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Imageless Thought</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://imagelessthought.github.io/mbaggett/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence: Demystifying AI, Machine Learning, and Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mbaggett/blog/artificial-intelligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mbaggett/blog/artificial-intelligence/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Artificial Intelligence (AI) is a multidisciplinary field focused on creating machines capable of performing tasks that traditionally require human intelligence. Its diverse applications range from natural language processing to image recognition, offering profound implications for various industries. Within the vast landscape of AI, Machine Learning (ML) stands out as a subset that emphasizes the development of algorithms enabling machines to learn from data and improve their performance.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Started with Github and Github Pages</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mbaggett/blog/github-announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mbaggett/blog/github-announcement/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://git-scm.com&#34; title=&#34;Git Website&#34;&gt;Git&lt;/a&gt; is a free and open source distributed version control system designed to handle everything from small to very large projects with speed and efficiency. Git is widely used for collaborative software development and &lt;strong&gt;Github&lt;/strong&gt; is a very popular Git platform. Git is used to track changes, keep a complete history of the changes, and allows you to roll back to any point. Owners can grant access to a project and allow others to submit changes: those changes can be reviewed by the owner and merged, rejected, or a separate branch created.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jekyll: Static Webpages</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mbaggett/blog/jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mbaggett/blog/jekyll/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://jekyllrb.com/&#34; title=&#34;Jekyll Website&#34;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt; is a free and open source static site generator that was developed by Github and is written in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ruby-lang.org/en&#34; title=&#34;Ruby Programming Language&#34;&gt;Ruby Programming Lanaguage&lt;/a&gt;. It takes text written in &lt;a href=&#34;https://daringfireball.net/projects/markdown/&#34; title=&#34;Markdown Website&#34;&gt;Markdown&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Shopify/liquid/wiki&#34; title=&#34;Liquid Website&amp;quot;&amp;gt;Liquid&#34;&gt;Liquid&lt;/a&gt;, HTML &amp;amp; CSS and uses standardized layouts to create static webpages. &lt;a href=&#34;https://sass-lang.com/&#34; title=&#34;SASS Website&#34;&gt;SASS: Syntactically Awesome Style Sheets&lt;/a&gt; integration is bulit-in. You can easily customize the look and feel, URLs, and the data displayed on your pages.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Generative AI and Microsoft Copilot</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mbaggett/blog/ms-linkedin-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mbaggett/blog/ms-linkedin-ai/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Generative AI and Microsoft Copilot This document is an article that explains the concept, history, and applications of generative AI, a type of AI that can create new content. It also introduces Microsoft Copilot, a tool that uses generative AI to assist users with various tasks in Microsoft 365 applications.&#xA;What is Generative AI? Generative AI is a paradigm shift for the future of work, where humans supervise and machines generate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Python for Non-Computer Science Students</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mbaggett/blog/python/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mbaggett/blog/python/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the world of Python programming! This tutorial is designed for undergraduate students who may not have a background in computer science but want to learn the basics of Python. Python is a versatile and powerful programming language that has gained widespread popularity for its simplicity, readability, and flexibility. Python is beginner-friendly and widely used in various fields, including data science, web development, and automation. It was created by Guido van Rossum and first released in 1991, with the goal of making programming accessible and enjoyable. Named after the British comedy group Monty Python, the language has evolved into a dynamic and user-friendly tool used across various domains of information technology.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to YAML for Non-Computer Science Students</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mbaggett/blog/yaml/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mbaggett/blog/yaml/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;YAML, short for &amp;ldquo;YAML Ain&amp;rsquo;t Markup Language&amp;rdquo; or sometimes &amp;ldquo;Yet Another Markup Language,&amp;rdquo; is a human-readable data serialization format. It is often used for configuration files and data exchange between languages with different data structures. YAML files use indentation and colons to denote structure, making them easy to read and write.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Digital Signage</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mbaggett/blog/digital-signage/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mbaggett/blog/digital-signage/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The signage solution we have in place has served us well but it is time for an update. The original open source developer of the solution has taken their project proprietary as well. We will be developing the new solution as open source and will use already available code whenever possible: don&amp;rsquo;t reinvent the wheel.  Unless you have to, that is.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Subsystem For Linux</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mbaggett/blog/windows-subsystem-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mbaggett/blog/windows-subsystem-linux/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Over the past two years years Microsoft has made some significant improvements to the &lt;b&gt;Windows Subsystem for Linux&lt;/b&gt;. The Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL) is a feature of the Windows operating system that enables you to run a Linux file system, along with Linux command-line tools and GUI apps, directly on Windows, alongside your traditional Windows desktop and apps. &lt;b&gt;WSL 2&lt;/b&gt; is a new version of the Windows Subsystem for Linux architecture, available beginning with Windows 10-Version 1903-Build 18362, that powers the Windows Subsystem for Linux to run ELF64 (Executable and Linkable Format) Linux binaries on Windows. WSL2 provides a truly great resource for developers and application testing.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
