<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Getting Started on Imageless Thought</title>
    <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/categories/getting-started/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Getting Started on Imageless Thought</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/categories/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence: Demystifying AI, Machine Learning, and Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/blog/artificial-intelligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/blog/artificial-intelligence/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Artificial Intelligence (AI) is a multidisciplinary field focused on creating machines capable of performing tasks that traditionally require human intelligence. Its diverse applications range from natural language processing to image recognition, offering profound implications for various industries. Within the vast landscape of AI, Machine Learning (ML) stands out as a subset that emphasizes the development of algorithms enabling machines to learn from data and improve their performance.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows Subsystem For Linux</title>
      <link>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/blog/windows-subsystem-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://imagelessthought.github.io/mainroad/blog/windows-subsystem-linux/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Over the past two years years Microsoft has made some significant improvements to the &lt;b&gt;Windows Subsystem for Linux&lt;/b&gt;. The Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL) is a feature of the Windows operating system that enables you to run a Linux file system, along with Linux command-line tools and GUI apps, directly on Windows, alongside your traditional Windows desktop and apps. &lt;b&gt;WSL 2&lt;/b&gt; is a new version of the Windows Subsystem for Linux architecture, available beginning with Windows 10-Version 1903-Build 18362, that powers the Windows Subsystem for Linux to run ELF64 (Executable and Linkable Format) Linux binaries on Windows. WSL2 provides a truly great resource for developers and application testing.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
